'Cause I already know
what he'll say.
(whining voice):
"Wah, wah, wah,
you shouldn't do it."
It's just like he's here!
(Raj:)Okay, so we know
that previous attempts
(Raj:)to send a message into space,
like the Golden Record
on Voyager,
were heavily criticized.
(Leonard:)Well, aliens could only play
the Golden Record
(Leonard:)if they figured out
how to build a record player.
(Raj:)Eh. Although, to be fair,
I watched E.T. build a telephone
(Raj:)out of a Speak & Spell
and an umbrella.
(Raj:)Dude was like
a little brown MacGyver.
(Leonard:)That would be more helpful
if E.T. were real.
(Raj:)Well, my feelings were real
when he was about to die.
(Leonard:)My God, when he's on the table
and they use the paddles on him.
(Raj:)And he's all white.
(Leonard:)They zip him up in that bag.
(Raj:)And Gertie can't stop crying.
(Leonard:)The flower dies.
(Raj:)Okay, let's talk
about something else.
All right, all right.
So it-it sounds
(Leonard:)like we need a way
to communicate that's simple.
(Raj:)And doesn't require
outside machinery
(Raj:)to be built to access it.